T.me/Moviezindian
What are you looking at?
It's cancer
Not some pretty girl's
Instagram page
How long have I got?
Three years.
Maybe
The Indian government has made
the shocking decision today
to revoke Kashmir's special status
The Indian Parliament has unilaterally
announced Articl 370 is abrogated
Pakistan's Foreign Affairs Office has
condemned this unilateral action and said
that Pakistan will weigh up all
options and give a befitting response
Article 370 canceled
How can India do that?
This is wrong, sir
This is not wrong
It's a declaration of war
You said three years, right?
It’s long enough
Time for diplomacy has passed, sir.
If we wait for the UN resolution.
then India will take control of our Azad Kashmir next.
A man of God cannot cha enge them
A man God cannot challenge them
It's time to befwend the Devil
General Qadir for you
General Qadir, all in order?
Don't want order,
I want chaos
What do you want?
You sure?
Once that bullet is fired,
It won't go back into the gun
You need to be sure.
Can you do it?
It'll take time,
but it can be done
A radar can’t detect it,
no signal can stop it
It fears nothing, nor can it be
reasoned with.
Once it's launched,
it's like a djinn from Hell
Countdown to Judgement Day starts
Good. Jim will let you know
where to deliver it
Why? Doesn't he trust you?
Jim?
If God asked him to
name anything he wanted,
he'd say,
"Are You playi g a trick on me”?
Jim keeps his cards
close to his chest
Boss, is this man "Raafe"?
Why?
One man come.
He asked for Raafe
We say don't know Raafe
He say Raafe come to see Fayyad
Where is he?
VIP area, getting special treatment
Who are you"?
Hey, Hindi.
Speak up1
Talk in Hindi!
No fun swearing at you in Arabic
You'll take 5 seconds
to be surprised.
5 seconds to wonder where
you've heard this voice
And 5 more seconds
to get over your disbelief
Then you'll ask,
"Pathaan? You?"
Still alive
Where is she"?
How did you s rvive
Answer my question first.
Where is Rubai?
Uff! Mr Pathaan has a broken heart.
Love and perfume cannot be concealed.
She's far from your reach
Now you'll be going far away too
Any last message?
I have a gift for her
Your dancing bells are undone,
Raafe So dance!
Kill him!
What are you waiting for?
Kill him.
There's a storm coming, Raafe.
Fasten your seat belt.
Closed the door!
my way, B^run.
If you go on about the cake,
how can I finish my work?
Light the candles.
Start singing "Happy Birthday",
and I'll be home before
the candles go out
Ma' am, I've got all the information.
And it seems there's no problem.
Yeah. Check again.
I need all the information now.
Run it past the Finance Ministry.
Ma'am?
Ma'am'?
We have a red flag.
Our scanner has just identified someone
Our scanner has just identified someone.
Who is it?
Rubai?
Where?
Paris A security camera
at Palais Royal metro station.
- When?
-15 minutes ago, max.
Get a team on it right away.
Keep eyes on her. Do not intercept.
Get
ne.
Use the blue c nel. We need
permission for i ediate take-off
Yes, ma'am.
And ye
..to keep you a slice of cake in the fridge.
How much longer?
5 hours, max.
-	Ma'am?
-	Hmm?
Ma'am are we going after Pathaan?
What do you know about Pathaan?
Not much, ma'am.
Whenever he's mentioned,
everyone gets uncomfortable.
They change the subject.
Ma'am...is he on our side?
He was once.
Not just on our side,
he was our centre-forward
Opening batsman, opening bowler,
wicketkeeper and four slip
fielder too.
You know,if it weren't for Pathaan,
we would not be doing
what we do.
Nor would the JOCR Department exist
Two years ago, during a Myanmar mission,
Pathaan got badly injured
He lay in a hospital for weeks It was touch and go.
Everyone believed the Pathaan chapter was closed.
he was writing a whole new book.
I heard you got badly hurt.
Ma’am, yes.
I have a metal plate in my foot,
a titanium disc in my neck.
nd bio-absorbabl scrwes in my shoul
But you look very well.
It's tough My body goes beep. beep,
beep at airport security.
They keep detecting metal.
Looks like reti en doesn't suit you
Why?
Retirement can be peaceful, Pathaan.
There are so many ways to spend one's time.
Tomorrow we could be a MasterChef
and Indian Idol the next day
You need to get a hobby, Pathaan.
Is that Punjabi?
Japanese know you know what it means
I know
If precious 'Ottery breaks,
the Japanese put the broken pieces
together with molten i Id
The object looks stronger and more beautiful.
It's even considered more valuable.
Ma'am, look at this file
These are the broken pieces
of our organisation.
The ’ e s. diers like me.
Forced to retire because of injury or trauma
But they're not done yet.
They're still full of guts and passion
They’re ready to fight and die for india
So what do you want?
To form a new unit?
Yes, ma’am.
Do you realise how many people will nedd convincing?
There'll be so much red tape,
your hands will get glued to
Try it.
You think I've just been growing my hair out?
I've tried it. And better,
I've dont it
"Joint Operations and Covert Research" ma'am
No, ma'am.
Just returning my boss her chair
You were looking for a new ho y
Try Kintsugi, please.
These broken soldiers need new eaning in their lives
They're ready for a mission
You are the molten gqld who can put them toge her
Stronger than before.
more dangerous
That was the birth of Team JOCR
Every important mission for India
that was our playground.
We had no rules to stop us
So obviously anyone who loved rules
had a problem with us. Like our Colonel Luthra
Wow!
Beautiful
Very beautiful
This space was reserved for a recreational
club for us and other departments1
A gym, sauna, pool tables, etc.
auna? Pool tables?
Excuse me, sir, you can't be serious
- These people are my officers .
-They're not officers.
You've made JOCR with some broken jokers
They're just broken eggshells
How dare you!
Good invention, guys
- Rishi, well done! -Thankyou, sir
- Did you think I actually.
- No, ma'am.
Oh, come on, Pathaan I was just playing along
Would I talk to a superior like that?
No. never
Don't be a child.
I admit Rishi's invention is very real
But Pathaan. you can't mess with me
- Is this a bad time?
- No, sir.
He looks a little pale
And he has those bags under his eyes, which you guys missed
Have you seen
Luthra's double chin?
It hangs down to his belly
And Luthra's paunch?
Very good.
Very serious department
Now I can make my recommendations to the Defence Secretary
I told you you're broken eggshells.
That's all
Paunch, ma'am!
Sir. Sir.
Sir. now that you're here, wait two minutes, please
I must show you something
Aeroflot 394C -144 casualties
Daeshca camed it was their doing
Daesh claimed it was their doing
Norwegian ship, Asgard
Pirates de
he Gulf o
Biggest ecological disaster of the decade.
Courtesy Boko Haram.
Chemical attack on the Japanese
The Japanese outfit Aleph claimed responsibility.
You think I have no intel on all this?
No, sir It wasn't Aleph
Or  Boko Haram or Daesh
At least, they weren't directly involved.
They outsourced these attacks to a private terrorist group
They wo k ®n contract, not for ideological reasons
Really?
errorists are corporations now?
Let's say a group like this exists, so what?
They’re Interpol's problem, not India’s.
Actually sir, now it is.
ually sir, now it is
Because their next episode s an India special
And this is a big one.
Sir, through the darknet we found out that
Outfit X is planning something big in Dubai.
At the Asian Scientific Confere
two Indian scientists will repre nt India and our...
At the  conference our President
ing the keynote address
They're after the President.
We Think so, sir.
I'll make sure the security is tripled.
They won't get near the President
-Thankyou, sir.
-Thank you.
Another request, sir
these...
eggsh
e with e
Trust me, Luthra.
You look after the President's security.
I changed the President's travel itinerary at the last minute
No sign of explosives
There are no spots for a siper to hide
Absolutely nothing suspicious
Intel was real, sir
But now there's radio silence
They've become more careful or.
Sir, you said you changed the President's travel route
What was it before?
He was to travel with the two scientists
and the press
Showing support for science.
Now he's taking another route
With full security
What about our scientists'?
Will they travel with the President"?
No. Multiple vehicles make security tricky
I want our NSG commandos to focus on the President
So the two scientists who had NSG cover,
no longer have it
Damn it’
They tricked us into changing the travel itinerary.
eir target is not the President, sir.
I was hoping to take a selfie with the President
with the President
and impress the missus’
You still want to impress her, after thirty years'?
Science s ea y Farooqui. Love is hard
Sir, we've been attacked.
You were right, Pathaan.
They've attack d the scientists' convoy
Lock me to the scientists' phone
- On it sir
- Now'
Wait. Don't shoot!
Wait Don’t shoot!
Dr. Sahani, Dr. Farooqui.
Take my advice.
Be more scared than you are
You're pretty screwed.
He's got the scientists in a grey Hummer. Pathaan
Sir, I've sent you the Hummer’s location
There's the Hummer sir
Pathaan, I've been waiting for a long time to meet you
I heard a lot about you when I was in RAW.
They call me "Jim"
Jim?
You probably heard I was dead.
So?
Well, I am actually dead for India
Here's the proof.
Bravery award.
I died a bloody hero
How come, Jim?
-I heard you...
- ...were the best?
You heard right I still am
She broke my heart
She'll break yours too.
The difference is I considered myself her lover,
and you think you're her s
Mother India!
You're lucky.
You'll die believing your patriotism meant something.
I'm sure they'll t for bravery on
medal for bravery you grave
They'll call you a martyr.
But cost to the country?
Zero.
If life was different, perhaps we'd be friends.
What a pity!
We have to play the cards we're dealt.
And in this round, I hold all the aces.
Raza! Rishi!
Rishi
- My seat belt.
-I was stuck.
Pathaan, my seat belt.
Rishi'
- My legs are stuck.
- Come on
My leg is stuck, sir.
Rishi.
- My leg is stuck.
- Rishi.
Pathaan!
Sir, my leg is stuck.
Sir my leg is stuck.
- We must go Pathaan!
-Wait1
- Raza'
- The car is about to explode!
- Raza!
- Take him away!
- There's nothing you can do.
Pathaan, we must go.
- Go, sir.
Nothing we can do
Sir, it's been an honour.
We must go, Pathaan!
Pathaan!
Jai Hin
Block the road.
These choppers won't fly through the tunnel.
they'll crash int he building.
key'll r to the buildin
Well, Pathaan? What next?
Their lives hang by this rope.
Only you can untie the knot
So, what's it gonn be. budd
mpnon sense?
Say hello to Mother India
Tell her I'm coming soon
I've a score to settle.
Jim.
Can't trust dead men to stay dead.
Was m working for RAW?
Jim and Kabir.
Our best agents.
They were quite similar
Calculative, precise, methodical
He first listens to his heart, then to his superiors.
- So, what went wrong? -A job.
So, what went wrong?
Remember the ONCC drilling team
the Somalian priates kidnapped?
Jim went solo
He managed to save six hostages, totally unharmed.
The pirates swore to take revenge.
They finally tracked Jim down.
They asked for a ransom of 100 million in exchange for Jim and his wife
But we don't negotiate with terrorists
You love your country too much.
But your country,
no love you.
No! No!
No!
No. Please leave her
We never found Jim's body. So we assumed he was dead.
Jim was given a medal, the bravery award
One of his uncles received it.
Couldn't you have paid the ransom for an agent like him and his family?
Your department does not lack funds,
Our funds can't be wasted ersonal matters
Such honesty, sir!
What if it was a minister's family'?
Only the weak go down on their knees, Pathaan.
Not soldiers.
Your decision has convinced him that his actions are justified.
And now
Shweta, check for leads on the darknet.
- Raktbee
- What's that?
- Raktbeej. Sounds like a codeword.
- For a man? Or an object?
Have the dead in Dubai been identified?
Yes sir.
All ex-soldiers or secret agents.
They recently received money transfers.
From one account?
Yes. From a Pakistani doctor Rubina Mohsin
She lives in London.
Her account was inactive for months. Then these transfers were made
Who knows if she was even awar
The bank would've alerted her about the transfers.
We've hacked her emails. She hasn't logged in for a month.
Her phone is off too
She's taking a flight
Where to?
t was sh be o
5hje‘ be off
If it was another agent, she'd be lea or Syria.
As it’s you -
it's Spain.
I'm desperate for a vacation.
Tonight
life is complete
In this instant
life is rich
My heart has been robbed
by m lovers
How they torment me
Tnese crazy thoughts of mine
The moment I feel a wave of modesty
throw it to the ind
The world has not seen my true colours
Shweta, I'm sending you info on Dr. Rubina Mohsin. Check it.
I'm like a breath of fresh air
My style, my habits all new
I never  follow the right path
The path of wrong sopfWting
Tonight...
In this instant
In this mst
life is rich
When I feel a wave of modesty
I throw it to the wind
The world has not seen my true colours
Throw a few seeds on the
ground and the ants come drawing
A bank account, a SIM can
And Pathaan appears in flesh and blood.
The hunter...
hunted!
Meet my team, Pathaan
Sergei, ex-SBU.
Begio, ex-AISE.
Detrich ex-BDD.
And Rubai, ex-ISI.
The world's top-secret agencies
are all represented here.
Are you for real?
Actually I came here to offer you a position
in a 6ft hole I've dug for you. .
There's room to lie down too
I you come half naked like this?
Or must I drag you out?
Yotrdo too.
Since t ay you becam a soldier.
That's all that Mother India offers
Only the names of the corpses change.
See Pathaan
We're not answerable
to anyone Family, foe or friend.
We choose the jobs we want.
And de t pri e we want.
Join us. Pathaan
Be rich. Be powe
Pay up. g ys
I wagered you'd refuse my offer.
Even your death win me a bet
Sorry, Pathaan
If you're not on my side can't afford
to let you be against me
Sorry, Pathaan.
Nothing personal
Women!
Yours, ma'am
Are you ex-ISI?
Not ex.
You thought you were the only ones monitoring Outfit X.
I've  been with them for a year, undercover.
Why all this?
With you. we'll get what I want faster
When did we beco e a we"?
When did we become a 'we”?
When I saved your life.
You endangered it
You know that, right?
- Run.
- Where are you?
Run
- where are you?
W e are going?
-Wait'
- Duck
You aim well.
So do they.
Father!
Morning.
You were out for 18 hours.
Take it easy.
Fever's down.
No Infection. And luckily the bullet dn't touch any vital organ.
You were calling for your father and crying
You kept asking them to let your father go
Father
He was a journalist in the Middle East
He asked too many questions
Printed too many answers
So he was brutally tortured
and we were made to watch from the front row
Then you went to Pakistan with your mother and joined medical college
Dr. Rubina Mohsin.
Affer  that, to serve humanity.
you joined the ISI.
Oh. Of course
Cheers
Couldn't you find a cheaper
is we have big budgets
But seriously,
why did you save my life?
Aren't your good looks and personality enough?
Normally they are. I'm so sexy.
You said we’d get what you wanted faster with me.
So I want to know, what do "we" want?
Raktbeej.
Heard the name?
He was a demon.
Wherever a drop of his blood fell,
another Raktbeej was born
Basically, it was impossible to destroy Raktbeej.
Whatever this Raktbeej is. it's in Russia
In 7 days ..what?
Jim will take deliver bf Raktbeej in 7 day
Then all hell break loose
basicatl ehave...
Bottoms up!
Think you skipped school the day
they spoke about ISI and India.
You see we don't get on so well.
Besides, the first day we met, you put Jim's gun against my head. Remember?
So don't take it personally
ave few trust issues.
Some things are more important
than trust issues
Like these 7 day
So ar ou in?
Or are you out?
Russia's a big place
Do you know the address'? Any landmark?
You know Something
Vault 412, Moscow Woskwich Tower
You moust know the address
You were Posted in Russia for three years
What else do you know about me?
Do you want me to tell you everything now?
Scary
An ISI agent tells us there's something in Moscow that Jim’s after.
Yes, ma'am.
I've heard about R'aktbeej on the darknet.
Do you know what it is?
So, let's hope Whever it is. it stays unknown.
I know you're fcfrniliar with every corner of Russia
But Russia is still a friendly country and a crucial ally.
A scandal will not be tolerated in Moscow or in Delhi.
Ma'am you know
Jim Wants Raktbeej.
If he can't buy it. he'll steal it.
And if you get caught?
Don't try negotiating for me.
I'm not Jim.
Damn it!
Whatever Raktbeej is,
neither Jim nor ISI should get their hands on it.
Go, get it!
Welcome.
Sir. me show you around
Same to you.
-	For an English dictionary
-	Thank you, sir. Thank you.
You need anything, contact Andrei.
You have a great honeymoon
You didn't tell me we were on our honeymoon.
If you had denied it, it would've broken Andrei’s heart.
Look. What a stunning-view!
Wow!
I never thought I'd see such a big
building on my wedding night!
If you stay with me, there's more fun to come.
Many corporates have their offices in that building.
W08KWI0H TOWER
The 92nd loor
osts
The 92nd floor is hdme to the orld's most secure vault
The vault.is a 30ft x 30ft room
No y or explosive can open it
No laser can cut through.
No acid'burn through
Can't cut it, can't break it.
Can’t blow it up, can't burn it.
But. but. but. there's only one problem
The vault has a lock and key
but two different people have them
So when you need to open it.
an uncle brings the lock from his home
and an aunty brings the key
The lock and key meet like the union of the Ganges and Jamuna
So. must we steal both lock and key?
Yes, exactly
But there's a complication
The lock is 12 kms away in Uncle Grigr's Office
And the key is 16kms away with Aunty Karen
And of course, their offices are in opposite direction
And the best part?'
We must get to the vault in 10 minutes once we've stolen them
I love this sugar-free yoghurt.
As soon as the lock and key are removed.
a timer starts ticking.
Within 10 minutes, at FSB h someone must enter an "all-
a s, c e .
This confirms all's well and it's not Rubai and Pathaan
-	Or else...
-	Or else?
I lockdown T
Lock, key or prayer . nothing makes a nee.
Unless the system is re et in three places
Game over
How can we reach the vau in 10 minutes in Moscow tna
Step 1 To get to the main lock, we must first open another lock
To open tna.t we need Uncle Grigor's fingerprints
-Any cops in sight? -Why?
Because you’re looking like a bomb!
Have a blast. -Oh, I will.
jlLIOOQ
Step 2
Our key-holding Aunty Karen
- You'll seduce her?
- / wish
I'm not her type
She'll be knocked out by some sleeping pills
You are my Karen!
Good night, K-K-K-Karen.
Step 3 we need tow planes. And tow pilots
Absolute professionals
You picked this place?
Pilots? Right.
They're lats. Very professional.
Actually, flying is just their hobby
Professi , They're singers.
-	Singers?
-	Singers.
What about the bill?
Rubai, listen. You'll have some cheese?
Never mind It's fun.
Are you and the missus looking for anything in particular?
Very particular
How would you like to earn 20,000 boobies'?
Rubles'
What did I say?
I meant rdbles.
We have a meeting with Raktbeej. Our final step.
Tomorrow we have an appointment with Raktbeej, so..
Get some rest
This may be our last night outside a Russian jail.
Then we shouldn't waste it
Yeah! Waste is not good.
Maybe I..
Could you help with my bandages?
Bandages? Of course
Nothing better I'd like to do than change your bandages.
Pathaan.
I mean, you're actually a Pathaan?
Are you a Muslim’’
Rubai, I don't know what I am. Who I am.
Or who my parents were
Or why I was abandoned in front of a cinema.
Landed up in an orphanage, then a juvenile centre,
then a remand home
So, it was really my country that raised me
I wanted to be a good son
and serve my parents Pay them back
So I joined the Indian army
- I'm sorry.
- It’s OK
By the way.
what film was playing at the cinema where tiey left you?
You don't take emotions seriously'?
Do you?
Never
So how did you turn from Lawaaris to Khuda Gawah?
It was in 2002
I was in Afghanistan on a joint mission with the US army
My first mission
The US target that day was a Salauddin Hussemi
a Taliban leader
A missile was locked on to the location of his phone
This Mr. Husseini was a teacher in a madrasa
People started to run
The problem was there were
30 kids still in the madrasa
and the missile was to strike in one minute
The missile was heading for the madrasa
The kids were still inside
I was in a coma for a month
A day did not go by without someone in that village praying for me
Subhanallah
-	Adaab.
-	Salaam.
Everyone has been praying for your good health
I swear, no Pathaan mother
has ever given birth to someone as brave as you.
From today, we are yours and you are ours.
Our Pathaan
You know what?
Every year without fail I try
and celebrate Eid with everyone in that village
With my Pathaan family
Once we have the bag we have 10 minutes Don't forget
- Rubai, start your timer alarm
Karen, do you have a copy.
Who are you?
Rubai'
Rubai'.
I have a release malfunction
Rubai, when you're above the building, cut your rope.
Captain, listen to me.
Are you crazy?
Just do it.
What the ?
We're 90 seconds late In a minute the alarm will go off. Let's go!
We're 90 seconds late In a minute the alarm will go off Let’s go!
- Vault number? -412
How do these steps open?
No time for that
Here
Throw it to me
Pathaan,
I'm sorry.
It's impossible to open that vault
It is possible. For Pathaan
Pathaan? Why would he help you?
- Mat --check
You mean "checkmate ?
When the king tl inks the queen will sacrifice herself for him
all his concentration is on saving the queen
When the king realises the queen has switched sides, it'll be
Checkmate
The king is dead
The king is dead.
Pathaan was put into a high security prison
That's where I last saw him
He's not with us.
Oh please. Miss Grewal, we know he's Marcos’s agent
He was. He went rogue.
Do.you think we would sanction this stupidity?
Whatever he's done, we have no stake in it.
So you don't care how we deal with this situation?
Be my guest
And if this "situation" survives,
pump him with two bullets from me.
I'll reimburse you
going t crush your bones t owder
You're a dead man walking.
What was he saying?
I'm going to kill you.
Guys. Timeout, guys!
Please.
Stopped at a coffee sh p?
And a pharmac
And a pharmacy
Here. Painkillers
Men don't feel pain
Take them, brother
They're coming
You've taken it easy too long Let's get to work.
Tiger, he's got a grenade
- So what!
-I have the pin.
When will you stop pulling pins?
I'm sorry
I’m having a blast.
Are you9
Oh man!
Behind you!
Mission accomplished!
Did they come for you?
For you
You made big trouble, didn't you?
I'm a Pathaan
- Shall we run?
- Me first
You got scared, right?
I know.
For you.
Look back!
Run Pathaan. run.
T.me/Moviezindian
Listen
I'm going on a big mission.
Tiger may need Pathaan.
So stay alive.
I will. I’ll be there.
Oh, man I promise.
- Don't need promises.
- Then what?
I need those painkillers.
Oh, painkillers. It's here.
This is yours, this is mine.
Bitter isn't it
It's a painkiller. Not chewing gum
So, Tiger helped Pathaan in Russia?
How come Pathaan was missing for so long?
That was the first time anyone
had defeated Pathaan
He swore
without Rubai, Jim and Raktbeej
To maintain diplomatic relations with ussia
Pathaan's absence suited us.
And now?
The time of  Pathaan's exile is over.
"Pump him with two bullets from me."
What could I have said? Pathaan's like a son to me.
don't torture him too much."
Why did Luthra let you go to Russia?
Don't ask. He wanted to go himself
He would've shot you point-blank
if he knew the reason I went there wa to give you
a message.
He's not with us
Did Raafe tell you anything?
Jim bought two Saber missiles
He doesn't know why.
ot where Jim is
where she is.
Paris? When?
A e urs ago
Activity?
Walks, cafes.
Walks.
s she's waiting someone.
Perhaps st es waiting for so
n I have to go.
nt keep a girl waiting.
Pathaan, I do you stole from the Russians,
but I've never seen them so tense
Find it
Find Jim
Ma'am
Salaam Alaikum
Wa' alaikumu s- salaam.
May Peace be upon on you too
Thank you. Raza
In romantic Paris - two's company, three's a crowd
I must talk to her about the pleasures of love.
Alone
Thank you.
I fgured when I'd see you again,
d shoot you first,
then ask questions.
But you called me here your own accord, so
Of course, Rubai.
we conveniently got your photo at the Paris metro.
You knew I'd see that CCTV footage. And I would
come to you.
So well, I'm here. Tell me quickly what you have to say.
Raktbeej
You want to know what it is?
What is it?
• ••I
•••• ••••ft*
• •••
Smallpox?
It was eradicated in 1980.
Yes, but some research facilities still have samples of the virus,
in case we need to fight smallpox again.
The virus samples were in Russia.
We stole them.
But why?
Every country in this world has a vaccine against smallpox
In case of an emergency outbreak.
The vaccine works against the old smallpox virus.
Jim has mutated it.
The mutated virus is far more dangerous.
We have no vaccine against it. r No cure either.
That’s why he planned the big operation in Dubai to kidnap Dr. Sahani.
Who for? Who's paying him?
Do you know General Qadir?
It:s*time to befnienti the Devil
- Your government?
The General joined forces with ISI extremists
when India abrogated Article 370.
Pathaan I swear,
I had no idea at all
that my own people would do such a mad thing.
If this virus spreads,
how can Pakistan save itself?
He has changed the virus's DNA.
It does not follow the one-week pattern like Covid-19.
This kills within a few hours.
Anyone infected by this virus cannot go very far.
It decimates a whole city in a matter of days, once it spreads.
But it can also be contained within a city's borders
It attacks one city at a time.
Not the whole world.
But how, Rubai?
So why do you think I can trust you again?
I'm a soldier, Pathaan.
Like you,
I will do anything for my country.
But this?
Killing thousands of innocents? This is not my idea of war.
Trust me, Pathaan.
Just once more.
I'll always have my eye on you.
One wrong move...
I've made all the wrong moves I had to.
Now I want them erased.
Where's Jim?
He's meeting Dr. Sahani in his lab in two days.
Tell me about this lab.
Everything.
Rubai'
ooking good.
Aiwa s.
But you haven't noticed me before.
Who says love is only at first sight?
Want to drown in them?
I know the difference between the sea and lava.
Did you design the virus as instructed?
Are you really going to do this?
you really going to do this?
For money?
You think this is about money?
I could’ve easily robbed a bank blindfolded Doctor
I was asked a question once
"What's your price?
"The price of your family?
"Your child?"
Today you h my answer.
It's I who will decide the price of you life
Do you have ower to buy me? So buy me
This is crazy
These are your own people
Your own country
Oh, Doc! Country, borders, etceter
They exist to remind the weak to stay in their place
While the real machines keep turning:
power and control.
I don't care for any coun
My country is wherever I ha to be.
That’s my world.
Let me check.
If anything
?ia pens to these orbs, then c t our own throat.
Dr. Saham Dr Sahani.
Give me the orbs
The orbs are safe. Let's go
Jim, I was trying to
Raktbeej safe...
Normally when you lie, it's so smoothly done
I’m touched you're scared of me.
- Jim, trust me, I...
- Explain to your people
how you betrayed them.
General Qadir is not "my people".
When my people hear what he's done,
they'll bloody hang hi
I have a daughter.
I wanted you to stay alive for her sake.
Bag?
He must be close
Give it to me, Pathaan.
Giv o me, Pathaan.
No, sir. We have to destroy it.
Absolutely not.
Jim has mutated the smallpox virus.
so v/e' need to make a vaccine.
-1 don't think so, sir
- Give it to me.
Pathaan!
What the hell, sir?
What's going on?
She's ISI, PatRaan
We have the virus orb, thanks to her.
And thanks to her, the virus landed in Jim's hands.
She knows Jim's plans.
- We have to question her, Pathaan.
- Ma'am...
Besides, where can she go now?
Jim and the ISI are looking for her.
If we let her go, she won't survive for two days.
- Take her.
- Wait
Pathaan...
You'll be OK.
Pathaan's promise.
Ma'am, you'll have to wear this suit
Yes, Doctor?
I got your message
Come. Nandini must w y mething
There are three	layers
to get to the orb's core
- Did you cut through-?
- We got to the central core
- Di cut through?
- We got to the central core.
- Where the virus is.
- It was empty.
We analysed the liquid carefully It's water. Only water
What happened to the lights?
Ma'am, our system has been hacked.
There's an incoming video call
It's Jim.
Connect him
Hello, hello How's everyone?
Was it fun?
Finding only pure distilled mineral water in the orb?
Just following my plan in case anyone tried to force the orbs open
The orb has three layers
The first layer was empty
Only a vacuum.
The seuL.d 'a er a
It contained an invisible corrosive gas
It's an acid that melts plastic on contact.
Your plastic suits for example
The third layer contained my superstar
Raktbeej
The virus is now all over the lab
In the orb's center. you'll find clean safe mineral water
You won't feel thirsty when you're dying
You think I'm bluffing?
Look at your pretty white suits
Are they turning black?
Your suits are of no use now
The virus you were looking for in the water
is invading your whole body.
If pain is measured on a scale of 10.
you'll experience it at 13 or 14.
Exciting right?
A demo ofRaktbeej
So please, share your dying moments on Instagram and Twitter
Things that ares n - they sell.
Cheers
Lock down the lab.
Lock the lab!
All the others, get out’
All the others, get u .
others, get out
We're sealing the lab.
Get out! Get out all of you
We can decontaminate the atmosphere.
UV radiation, gamma rays.
But how can you decontaminate us. Luthra?
But how can you decontaminate us.
The virus is inside us
here s only one way.
Very few people get the chance to decide how they'll face their death.
With fear? Hesitation? Or will they panic?
I will not give a bloody terrorist that satisfaction
I'm a soldier
And now,
all of you are too
Everyone dies someday,
Today it's our turn
Accept it.
olonel, you know what to do.
Don't save RDX.
We'll be dead anyway
Just make sure the virus does not spread
Thank you, everyone.
It was a great honour serving with you
You're the molten gold that kept my life together.
Ma'am...
You are that gold now Pathaan
You'll keep everyone together
and make them strong.
You were always
the one who kept us together
Get Jim.
I promise, ma'am.
Make him die a death
far worse than ours
Ma'am.
In the name of Lord Shiva!
Hello, everyone
I know this is a bad time for all of you
I respect your pain
So. I'll do my best not to appear
too cheerful
But come on!
It was some Ian1
You should be imorssed
You were an Indian soldier Dammit'
And thanks to you. I'm an
Indian businessman now
If you survive, you might become a client of mine
Then I'll get you anything you want. Right now. I serve another client
I'm doing what he wants
Do you even realise what you're doing?
You're unleashing your wrath on humanity
History will remember you as a monster.
Oh ho' That never occurred to me
What can I do? Everything is ready
My Saber missile. Armed and TSady
It's in a location that only I know
It's in a Io at
An Indian city that only I know
Such a pity!
You blew up your lab before you could see what Raktbeej was capable of
But when it spreads in Delhi Mumbai. Hyderabad or Amritsar
what will you do?
Blow up those cities?
What do you want?
I want you to negotiate with a terrorist. Colonel Luthra.
You didn't do it for me Now you'll negotiate with me
What do you want?
What do you thlhk?
Kashmir
Obviously. Kashmir
You have 24 hours
After 24 hours. if a single soldier
a single tank, a single gun or the Indian flag is seen in Kashmir, then
That's impossible.
How can I make that happen in 24 hours?
We need time to think.
Perhaps I used the wrong word that's why you're confus
This is not a negotiation Colonel Luthra.
it's an ultimatum
Your time starts
The situation you're in, the fear that's overcoming, you
I've been there
No one took responsibility for the death of my wife and unborn child.
A now no one is responsible for your death
How does it feel, guys?
It's not appropriate to say "Jai Hind"
So. take care Time is running out.
Pathaan, you have to stop this madman.
Look! Your innocent family.
You know what we'll do to them?
Whichever city the missile strikes,
that's where your family will be.
Where is that missile?
was only to make payment
I said Jim would tell them where to deliver it.
If you don't know the city, you must know the country.
Where?
Afghanistan.
Father!
I am sorry, Rubai
Fear blinds people
But you can see
I'm not your contry
I know.
I shouldn't do this.
It's wrong.
I'm sorry.
Pathaan?
To you!
I said sorry.
All calm, General?
I don't want calm, I want havoc.
India will not give Kashmir, General.
do we teach them a lesson?
The missile is ready.
You just have to press the button and I have to get paid.
Then boom!
General.
Everyone in my village was struck by a strange disease
They're all dead now
A metal ball fell here and no one survived after that
What are they saying?
The video is from an Afghan village, some 200 kms away.
The local TV is saying
a strange virus is spreading through the village
It has the same symptoms as
smallpox.
That's...
that's impossible
Raktbeej.
How can it be Raktbeej?
One orb is on the missile,
e other was destroyed in India.
Either you're a fool,
or you think I am.
If you want all your money,
find out how this other Raktbeej landed there.
You're mistaken If you think I’m your friend,
or that I have sympathy towards Pakistan.
Or that I need money.
You haven't understood me, General.
I am the demon Raktbeej.
Leave me!
If you want to see a free show, why pick on Delhi?
Change the co-ordinates.
Let's party in Islamabad.
No, sorry. I'm sorry. Don't do that
You handle it yourself, right?
Exactly as you told me.
I don't know where it came from.
Find out what's going on.
Who's behind this?
I want the answer,
and his head.
want both.
Welcome'
To my home!
This is my Afghan family.
My people.
Our Pathaan.
What did you find there?
The man who stands before you.
Pathaan.
You have this nasty habit.
You smell a party and arrive
invited.
Never ever invited to a bash, Pathaan just loves to gatecrash
If you have a party
- in Pathaan's home
With some fireworks
Some joke, General!
Another of your agents has fallen in love with the enemy.
First there was Zoya and Tiger.
And now...
Has ISI turned into some dating website for Indian agents?
Pathaan!
- Raza.
- Pathaan.
Pathaan, Jim isn't a man to give up
There must be
e must be
Amol, see if the orb can be detached from the missile
Amol see if the orb can be d from the missile.
-	Yes sir
-	Duck
I'll deactivate the missile
Where's the orb?
Pathaan, the missile was only a diversion
The real Raktbeej isn't here
Where is Raktbeej? What is Jim's real plan?
You traitor, I will...
Wait! Only Sergei knows.
Sergei.
Flight LT-72.
Pathaan and Colonel Luthra listen to me
Raktbeej is on a plane
Flight LT-72. It's circling Delhi right now.
If the orb can be deactivated,
me to air traffic control Now!
Pathaan find Jim
Flight LT-72, do you hear me?
Ground Air Control, this is Captain Mehra from Flight LT-72.
Landing permission denied.
I repeat, landin permission denied.
What?
Raktbeej is sitting happily in a plane over Delhi now.
The orb has six minutes left
And so does Delhi
In six
ni
will spread through the plane's AC ducts
you can grab this detonator switch
What a pity!
It's unlikely
Captain Mehra, this is Colonel Luthra from RAW
There's a biological weapon on board
The devie is in your AC ducts
What?
What am I supposed to do, Colonel? We're running low on fuel.
Captain, you're carrying a very dangerous weapon.
Fly as far as you can from Delhi, please.
I found it, Colonel.
Only four minutes to go.
Get me the minister.
Yes, sir.
There is no other option.
Jai Hind.
- Connect me to missile command
- Yes, sir
Captain, we will have to destroy the plane.
There must be another way, Colonel.
I have 300 passengers
and many children on board.
Right now, your plane is more dangerous than a nuclear bomb.
I’m sorry. We...can't save you
Missile control, intiate strike protocol
Come on, Pathaan
There's only one option.
Remember how you sacrificed your scientists?
Play "Vande Mataram" on the plane
and blow up the passengers.
Fire.
My family's lives were sacrificed, Now it's your turn to make a sacrifice.
Farewell, Pathaan.
The timer has stopped, sir Please stop the missile
Abort, abort, abort!
Ladies and gentlemen this is your Captain here
Please buckle up because we're about to land in Delhi
You couldn't understand something very simple.
A soldier does not ask
what his country can do for him.
He asks
what he can do for his cou
You don't deserve this Jim
Give your Mother India my last goodbye.
Jai Hind
If anyone merits this medal, it's you
I've never met a braver soldier than you
Ma' am
Pathaan.
Colonel, good news.
I'm leaving.
So you won't suffer from acidity and blood pressure anymore
Our paths are separate now.
-Thankyou, sir
- The war is not over, Pathaan.
-We need you.
- Me
But we are... what did you call us? Broken eggshells'?
I admit mistakes were made, Pathaan.
But this country cannot be saved by Colonel Luthra alone.
Or by Tiger or Kabir.
Or even by Pathaan.
Everyone is needed
There are many soldiers like them, Pathaan.
Some with wounded bodies, others with damaged souls.
But they are ready to sacrifice their lives for this country.
These broken folk can only be put together with the gold
that has lived through fire.
And that person is you.
Make the sharpest sword, Pathaan,
so the souls' of the enemy tremble.
But who will wield that sword?
Who will it strike? How will it strike?
Who will it strike?
- How will it strike?
Who decides that?
The sword is yours.
Thank you. Thank you very much. sir.
- Let's start.
- Yes, sir.
Sorry, sir.
I have an urgent appointment.
With whom?
With my hairdresser.
You cutting your hair?
No, sir.
Only a shampoo.
T.me/Moviezindian
If you want to all m love
I ask only
my heart for permission
The ways of love
only the fortunate know
Risking my own life
I saved the enemy
Many people love to talk
-I know what's real, my friends
- My friends
Many people love to talk
but I know what's real
I can even stop the wind
The Lord showers you with orayers
When pathaan get into the groove my love
He steals all hearts
The promises he make my love
He'll stand by forever
When Pathaan get into the groove my love
He steals all hearts
The promises he make my love
Jn ro s he
my I ve
He'll stand by forever
I'll tell you how to win hearts my friends
I will tell you how
I'll tell you how to love the enemy
Just give me a sign
I'll give my heart to you twice over
Feeling of friendship have cast their spell
Even enemies turn to me for an embrace
When Pathaan gets into the groove my love
He steals all heart
The promises he makes my love
He'll stand by forever
When Pathaan gets into the groove.
He steals all hearts
The promises he makes, my love
He'll stand by forever
Can't do it anymore.
Yeah.
I've been thinking, it's been 30 years, we should stop.
But who’ll replace us?
There's that guy.
That guy.
What about that other guy?
He has something.
No, not him.
He's got no style. Nah!
Never mind.
And him?
Our country is at stake. We can't leave it to kids.
Let's go.
Lower back.